This firm will blow you away.
The Business is a drama, action, thriller film directed by Nick Love.
During the '80s, a young man named Frankie dreams of escaping London's South East
region, and his mother's thug of a boyfriend gives him just the opportunity.
After beating up the abusive beau, Frankie runs off to Spain, where he lands a job delivering a
package to the dapper Playboy Charlie, a gangster who takes him under his wing.
Working as Charlie's driver, Frankie is immersed in a world of fast cars
and pretty women -- but all the excess could be his undoing.
Frankie, played by Danny Dyer.
Charlie, played by Tamer Hassan.
Sammy, played by Geoff Bell.
Carly, played by Georgina Chapman.
Ronnie, played by Eddie Webber.
Danny, played by Adam Bolton.
The Business is a 2005 crime film written and directed by Nick Love.
The film stars Danny Dyer, Tamer Hassan and Roland Manookian, all of
whom were in Love's previous film The Football Factory.
Geoff Bell and Georgina Chapman also appear.
The plot of The Business follows the Greek tragedy-like rise and fall of a young cockney's career within a drug importing
business run by a group of British expatriate fugitive criminals living on the Costa del Sol in Spain.
The film explores themes of drug dealer, drug smuggling,
smuggling (contraband), cocaine, coast guard.
The tone is emotional and intense.